To convince Pihu, I made Bihi chaat.
But everything went wrong.  Because as
soon as I woke up this morning, Pihu
brought me straight to the Bihi tree.
But I ignored it and
came near the well, took a shower and went inside the house.  But
after this I had to immediately climb the tree
and pluck so many edible behis and
when I gave them to Pihu, she washed all the behis
thoroughly and brought them home and we were
cutting them to make chaat.  But suddenly something went
wrong and I had to
rush to the hospital immediately.  And
when we reached home after getting the neighbour brother who had come with us bandaged, Pihu immediately
brought some spices.
After putting it in and hurriedly tasting it, she said that she was
not enjoying it.
So she immediately picked up the packet of chilli powder.
Which after mixing it I will sweat.
This is correct.  But the problem arose
when
Pihu ate the spicy chaat after it fell on the bed.